Jack Benny papers, 1930-1974
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television scripts.
  - The Jack Benny Television Show.
    - ., January 26, 1958. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - ., February 9, 1958. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - ., February 23, 1958. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - ., March 9, 1958. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - ., March 23, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - ., April 6, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - ., April 20, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - --repeat telecast of December 6, 1963.., May 4, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - --repeat telecast of October 9, 1955.., May 18, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - --repeat telecast of January 9, 1955.., June 1, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - --repeat telecast of December 4, 1955.., June 15, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - ., September 21, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - ., October 5, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - ., October 19, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - ., November 2, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - ., November 16, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - ., December 14, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - ., December 28, 1958. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - ., January 11, 1959. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - ., January 25, 1959. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - ., February 8, 1959. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - ., February 22, 1959.; 2 copies. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - ., March 8, 1959. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - ., March 22, 1959. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - ., April 5, 1959. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - ., October 4, 1959. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - ., October 18, 1959. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - ., November 1, 1959. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - ., November 29, 1959. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - ., December 13, 1959. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - ., December 27, 1959. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - ., January 10, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - ., January 24, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - ., February 7, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - ., February 21, 1960.; 2 copies. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - ., March 6, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - ., April 3, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - ., April 17, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - ., May 1, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - ., October 16, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - ., October 23, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - ., October 30, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - ., November 6, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - ., November 20, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - ., November 27, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - ., December 4, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - ., December 25, 1960. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - ., January 1, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - ., January 8, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - ., January 22, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - ., January 29, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - ., February 5, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - ., February 12, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - ., February 19, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - ., February 26, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - ., March 5, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - ., March 12, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - ., March 19, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - ., March 29, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - ., January 28, 1962. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - ., February 4, 1962. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - ., April 2, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - ., April 9, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - ., April 16, 1961. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - ., October 15, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - ., October 22, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - ., November 5, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - ., November 12, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - ., November 19, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - ., November 26, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - ., December 3, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - ., December 10, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - ., December 17, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - ., December 24, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - ., December 31, 1961. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - ., January 7, 1962. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - ., January 14, 1962. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - ., January 21, 1962. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - ., January 28, 1962. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - ., February 4, 1962. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - ., February 11, 1962. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - ., February 18, 1962. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - ., March 4, 1962. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - ., March 11, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - ., March 18, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - ., March 25, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - ., April 1, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - ., April 8, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - ., April 15, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - ., April 22, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - ., September 25, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - ., October 2, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - ., October 9, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - ., October 16, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - ., October 23, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - ., October 30, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - ., November 13, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - ., November 20, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - ., November 27, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - ., December 4, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - ., December 11, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - ., December 18, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - ., December 25, 1962. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - ., January 1, 1963. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - ., January 8, 1962. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - ., January 15, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - ., January 22, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - ., January 29, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - ., February 5, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - ., February 12, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - ., February 19, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - ., February 26, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., March 5, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., March 12, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., March 19, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., March 26, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., April 2, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., April 9, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., September 24, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., June 21, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., October 8, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., October 15, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., October 22, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., October 29, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., November 5, 1963. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - ., November 19, 1963. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - ., November 26, 1963. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - ., December 3, 1963. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - ., December 10, 1963. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - ., December 24, 1963. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - ., December 31, 1963. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - ., January 7, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - ., January 14, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - ., January 21, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - ., February 4, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - ., February 11, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - ., February 18, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - ., February 25, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - ., March 3, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - ., March 17, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - ., March 31, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - ., March 31, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - ., April 7, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - ., April 14, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - ., April 21, 1964. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - ., September 25, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - ., October 2, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - ., October 9, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - ., October 16, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - ., October 23, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - ., October 30, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - ., November 6, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - ., November 13, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - ., November 20, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - ., November 27, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - ., December 4, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - ., December 11, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - ., December 18, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - ., December 25, 1964. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - ., January 8, 1965. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - ., January 22, 1965. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - ., January 29, 1965. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - ., February 5, 1965. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - ., February 12, 1965. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - ., February 19, 1965. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - ., February 26, 1965. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - ., March 5, 1965. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - ., March 12, 1965. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - ., March 26, 1965. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - ., April 2, 1965. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - ., April 16, 1965. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Shower of Stars.
    - ., October 6, 1955. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - ., November 3, 1955. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - ., November 1, 1956. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - ., June 10, 1957. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - ., March 14, 1957. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - ., April 11, 1957. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - ., October 31, 1957. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - ., January 9, 1958. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - ., February 13, 1958. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - ., March 20, 1958. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - ., April 17, 1958. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Outside Telecasts.
    - -- The George Burns Hour.., October 31, 1958. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - -- The Jack Benny Hour.., March 18, 1959. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - -- The Jack Benny Hour.., May 23, 1959. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - -- The Jack Benny Hour.., November 7, 1959. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - -- The George Gobel Show.., December 20, 1959. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - -- The Jack Benny Hour.., March 19, 1960. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - *-- The Jack Benny Hour.., March 18, 1959. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - *-- The Jack Benny Hour.., May 23, 1959. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - *-- The Jack Benny Hour.., November 7, 1959. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - *-- The Jack Benny Hour.., March 19, 1960. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - *-- The Jack Benny Hour.., May 23, 1959. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - -- The Jack Benny Hour.., November 3, 1965. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - -- The Jack Benny Hour.., December 1, 1966. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - --The Hollywood Palace.., February 4, 1967. (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Audiovisual Materials.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  SERIES CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Jack Benny Radio Broadcasts., (14 tapes)
    - The Canada Dry Program,., 1932-1933. (Box 58, Volume 1)
      Broadcast on Monday and Wednesday evenings (later on Sunday and Thursday evenings) over the National Broadcasting Company. Point of origin: WJZ, New York City.
      - 1. 9:30-10:00 p.m., Eastern Time.., Monday, May 2, 1932,.; Tape made from 16 33-1/3 rpm transcription which was earlier made from 78 rpm discs.
        Cast: Jack Benny (Master of ceremonies).
        George Olsen and his orchestra.
        Ethel Shutta, Fran Frey, Bob Borger, Bob Wright (singers). _____Thorgerson (announcer).
        The remaining 77 shows in the Canada Dry series are missing from the collection.
    - The Chevrolet Program,., 1933.; Technical note: Tapes of this series were made from uncoated aluminium discs (12 78 rpm). Due to poor storage conditions prior to their donation to the University, many of these reference discs have suffered serious corrosion. This has acted to seriously degrade playback quality and has resulted in numerous instances of sticking and jumping of grooves. (Box 58, Volume II.)
      Broadcast Friday evenings, 10:00-10:30 p.m. Eastern time, over the National Broadcasting Company. Point of origin: WEAF, New York City.
      Regular cast: Jack Benny.
      Mary Livingstone.
      James Melton.
      Frank Black and his orchestra.
      Howard Claney (announcer).
      Programs 1-4, 6, 7, 9-13 & 16 missing from collection.
      - 5. --skit: She done him right.., March 31, 1933.; Closing tag is missing.
      - 8. --skit: Why gals leave home.., April 21, 1933.
        Guest: Edward G. Robinson.
      - 14. --skit: Who killed Mr. X - Part 2.., June 2, 1933.
        Added cast: Sam Hearn (Watson).
      - 15. --skit: Who killed Mr. X - Part 3.., June 9, 1933.
      - 17. --skit: End of season banquet.., June 24, 1933.
        Added cast: Johnny Woods.
    - The Chevrolet Program,., 1933-1934.; Technical note: Tapes of this series were made from uncoated aluminium discs (12 78 rpm). Due to poor storage conditions prior to their donation to the University, many of these reference discs have suffered serious corrosion. This has acted to seriously degrade playback quality and has resulted in numerous instances of sticking and jumping of grooves. (Box 58, Volume III.)
      Broadcast Sunday evenings, 10:00-10:30 p.m. Eastern time over the National Broadcasting Company. Point of origin: WEAF, New York City.
      Frank Parker.
      Alois Havrilla (announcer).
      Programs 1-9, 11-20 & 25 missing from collection.
      - 10. --skit: Uncle Tom's cabin.., December 10, 1933.
      - 21. --skit: My life as a floorwalker.., February 25, 1934.; First 5 minutes of program too damaged to transfer. Musical selections not recorded on discs.
      - 22. --skit: Duel between Jack and Frank Black.., March 4, 1934.
        Opening announcement, musical selections not recorded on discs.
      - 23. --skit: The haunted house.., March 11, 1934.
        Added cast: Sam Hearn (Ghostberg).
      - 24. --skit: Western skit.., March 18, 1934.
      - 26. --skit: The eternal triangle.., April 1, 1934.
        Guest: Eddie Cantor.
        Musical selections not recorded on discs.
    - The General Tire Program,., 1934.; Technical note: Tapes of this series were made from uncoated aluminium discs (12 78 rpm). Due to poor storage conditions prior to their donation to the University, many of these reference discs have suffered serious corrosion. This has acted to seriously degrade playback quality and has resulted in numerous instances of sticking and jumping of grooves. Certain shows (noted) were recorded on 12 78 rpm acetate coated discs and these are of better quality and are less damaged than the uncoated aluminium ones. (Box 58, Volume IV.)
      Broadcast Friday evenings, 10:30-11:00 p.m. Eastern time, over the National Broadcasting Company. Point of origin (unless otherwise noted): WEAF, New York City.
      Don Bestor and his orchestra (New York shows).
      Jimmie Greer and his orchestra (Hollywood shows).
      Don Wilson (announcer).
      Program 3, 8-15, 17, 19, 20 and 23 missing from collection.
      - 1. --skit: Frank Parker's music store.., April 6, 1934.
        Added cast: Sam Hearn (Ginsberg) (Discs too deteriorated in parts to transfer.)
      - 2. --skit: The bridge game.., April 13, 1934.
        Musical selections not recorded. (Opening of program too deteriorated to transfer.)
      - 4. --skit: Excerpt only, approximately 0:04-0:08 of program.., April 27, 1934.
        Remainder of program not in collection.
      - 5. --skit: The hills of old Kentucky--or Indiana--or anyplace.., May 4, 1934.
        Musical selections not recorded.
      - 6. --skit: Jack visits Don Wilson's mother.., May 11, 1934.; Acetate.
        Opening announcement and section approximately 1/3 into show not recorded.
        Last half of show missing.
      - 7. --skit: Jack and Mary visit Frank Parker's home.., May 18, 1934.; Acetate.
        Opening and closing announcements and musical selections not recorded.
      - 16. --skit: Who killed Mr. Stooge, cont.., July 20, 1934.
        Guests: Phil Baker, Harry McNaughton (Bottle), Ward Wilson (Beetle).
        Point of origin: KFI, Hollywood (7:30-8:00 p.m. Pacific Time).
        Short gaps in continuity caused by portions of discs too deteriorated to transfer.
      - 18. --skit: Train trip back to New York; Who killed Mr. Stooge, concluded.., August 3, 1934.; Acetate.
        Added cast: Sam Hearn (Schlepperman).
        Opening announcement and musical selections not recorded.
      - 21. --skit: The house of Rawchild.., August 24, 1934.; Lighting static throughout; acetate.
        Added cast: Sam Hearn (the Prince of Pilsner). Opening announcement and musical selections not recorded.
      - 22. --skit: The house of Benny.., August 31, 1934.
        Some sides recorded on turntable of uneven speed, hence considerable wow.
      - 24. --skit: Kiddie program.., September 14, 1934.
        Guest: Bert Wheeler, Johnny Woods.
      - 25. --skit: School days.., September 21, 1934.
        Guest: Johnny Woods.
      - 26. --skit: General Tire banquet.., September 28, 1934.
        Guests: Bert Wheeler.
        Opening and closing announcements and musical numbers not recorded.
        Despite mention of a new General Tire series to begin in March, this was the last such program.
    - The Jello Program,., 1934-1935.; (13 tapes); Technical note: Tapes of this series were made from uncoated aluminium discs (12 78 rpm). Due to poor storage conditions prior to their donation to the University, many of these reference discs have suffered serious corrosion. This has acted to seriously degrade playback quality and has resulted in numerous instances of sticking and jumping of grooves. (Box 59, Volume V.)
      Broadcast Sunday evenings, 7:00-7:30 p.m. Eastern time, over the National Broadcasting Company. Point of origin (unless otherwise noted): WJZ, New York City.
      Sam Hearn (Schlepperman).
      Don Bestor and his orchestra.
      Program 7, 9, 11, 12 and 14-40 missing from collection.
      - 1. --skit: The Jack Benny grocery store.., October 14, 1934.
      - 2. --skit: The Jack Benny grocery store, Part 2.., October 21, 1934.
      - 3. --skit: The Bennys of Wimpole Street.., October 28, 1934.
        Opening announcement and musical numbers not recorded.
      - 4. --skit: Through romantic Hawaii.., November 4, 1934.
      - 5. --skit: Charlie Chan in Radio City.., November 11, 1934.
      - 6. --skit: Mrs. Wiggs of the Onion Patch.., November 18, 1934.
        Guest: Mitzie Green.
        Musical numbers, except Mitzie Green's, not recorded.
      - 8. --skit: Rose of the Rio Grand Street.., December 2, 1934.
      - 10. --skit: Russia through a keyhole.., December 16, 1934.
        Musical selections, except Benny's, not recorded.
      - 13. --skit: The Count of Monte Crisco.., January 6, 1935.
    - The Jello Program,., 1935-1936.; Technical note: Tapes of this series were made from uncoated aluminium discs (12 78 rpm). Due to poor storage conditions prior to their donation to the University, many of these reference discs have suffered serious corrosion. This has acted to seriously degrade playback quality and has resulted in numerous instances of sticking and jumping of grooves. Certain shows (noted) were recorded on 12 78 rpm acetate coated discs and these are of better quality and are less damaged than the uncoated aluminium ones. (Box 59, Volume VI.)
      Kenny Baker.
      Johnny Greene and his orchestra.
      Programs 1-19, 22-23, 28 and 36 missing from collection.
      - 20. --skit: Sargeant Benny of the Northwest Mounted.., February 9, 1936.; Acetate.
        Guest: Benny Rubin.
      - 21. --skit: Two 4-minute excerpts; remainder of program missing from collection.., February 16, 1936.
      - 24. --skit: Income Tax Office; Jack takes Kenny to the Central Park Zoo.., March 8, 1936.; Badly damaged acetate.
      - 25. --skit: Banquet at the French Embassy.., March 15, 1936.
        Point of origin: Washington, D.C.
      - 26. --skit: Why Nell left home.., March 22, 1936.
        Point of origin: Baltimore, Maryland.
        Opening announcement and musical numbers not recorded. Program is incomplete. (2 of 4 sides missing).
      - 27. --skit: Cinderallen.., March 29, 1936.
      - 29. --skit: Ah wilderness.., April 12, 1936.
        Point of origin: Cleveland, Ohio.
        Last 3 minutes of program not recorded.
      - 30. --skit: Incomplete program; 4 of 7 sides missing.., April 19, 1936.
        Closing announcement not recorded.
      - 31. --skit: The Boston tea party.., April 26, 1936.
        Point of origin: WBZ, Boston.
        Pat Weaver substitutes for Don Wilson as announcer.
        WJZ local commercial replaces closing network commercial.
      - 32. --skit: The code of the hills.., May 3, 1936.; Acetate.
        Guests: Frank Parker, Don Bestor.
        Fourth anniversary program.
        WJZ cutaway as in program 31.
        Lightning static.
      - 33. --skit: Mother's day.., May 10, 1936.
        Point of origin: WXYZ, Detroit (acetate).
      - 34. --skit: Jack returns to Hollywood.., May 17, 1936.; Acetate.
        Incomplete; 4 of 7 sides missing.
      - 35. --skit: Tour of New York City.., May 24, 1936.; Acetate.
        Incomplete; 3 of 7 sides missing.
      - 37. --skit: Bennymount Pictures.., June 7, 1936.
        Point of origin: NBC studios, Hollywood.
        These Hollywood shows were recorded off the air (KFI) at 7:30-8:00 p.m. This is explained by the fact that the Benny programs, like many other radio shows of the period, were actually done twice, once for convenient listening in the eastern part of the country, then repeated for Western listeners 2 or 3 hours later.
        Guests: Leo Robin and Ralph Ranger.
        Orchestra's 2nd number and close of program not recorded.
        Incomplete; 1st of 4 sides missing.
        12 33-1/3 acetate transcriptions dubbed from 78's.
      - 38. --Incomplete; middle (approximately 8 minutes) missing.., June 14, 1936.
        First 30 seconds and orchestra's numbers not recorded.
        12 33-1/3 acetate transcriptions dubbed from 78s.
      - 39. --Closing show of season.., June 21, 1936.; 12 33-1/3 acetate transcriptions dubbed from 78s.
        Guest: Mitchell Leisen.
        Baker's song not recorded.
    - The Jello Program.., (5 tapes) (Box 60, Volume VII.)
      Program 16 and 17 missing from collection.
      - 1. --Introductory program; reporter bit; Mary's tonsils; phone call from her doctor; Kenny's girl Lena; guest star, trans-Atlantic flyer; Anthony Adverse trailer.., October 4, 1936.
      - 2. --Jack reads wires and reviews on first broadcast; sketch - Anthony.., October 11, 1936.
      - 3. --Big broadcast of 1937, finishing with phone call from Dad; synopsis of first installment, Anthony Adverse; final Installment.., October 18, 1936.
      - 4. --Conceited routine; bit with Ben Blue; preview of Romeo and Juliet, finishing with phone call from Lawton Campbell; announcement of minstrel show.., October 25, 1936.
      - 5. --Halloween routine and election bit; minstrel show, finishing with Romeo and Juliet in blackface.., November 1, 1936.
      - 6. --Sensitive routine; Mary reads letter from her mother; schoolroom sketch, Girls dormitory with Patsy Flick.., November 8, 1936.
      - 7. --Finishes previous week's program; reminiscing routine about school days; Kenny's first anniversary - roller skates; start Buck Benny interrupted by Italian, policeman and lawyer.., November 15, 1936.
      - 8. --Palm Springs routine; Mary recites Thanksgiving poem; Phil arrives late - call from Carole Lombard; sketch - Buck Benny rides again.., November 22, 1936.
      - 9. --Courtesy routine; Jack does a Mae West on the phone, kidding Phil; announces English sketch but switches to Buck Benny.., November 29, 1936.
      - 10. --Filling station routine; Kenny comes in late with Phil, Jack refusing to talk to Phil; start their argument; Mary gets phone call from her mother; society drama, Money ain't everything (aboard yacht) which segues into Buck Benny.., December 6, 1936.
      - 11. --Jack is late for broadcast; tune in his home and Chinese valet answers; Jack comes up to studio looking for his hat; phone call from Lombard; Buck Benny - Andy Devine's first appearance on the program.., December 13, 1936.
      - 12. --Dual personality routine; Jack refuses to make up with Phil; recites poem, Bear it with a grin; Christmas presents; Patsy tries to sell Jack a suit; Phil presents Jack with platinum wrist watch.., December 20, 1936.
      - 13. --Christmas muffler gifts; Mary reads letter from her mother; Jack receives wire from all his radio friends; gives Phil one of his mufflers; Buck Benny rides again.., December 27, 1936.